One dream, one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, you've got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
This is Gloom Island,
located on the Grand Mine.
When the Straw Hats were separated for
two years, Zoro trained himself here.
In an old castle near a
lake in this fallen country,
an enigmatic man passes his days.
He is a member of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
and said to be the strongest
swordsman in the world.
His name is Dracule Mihawk.
Moria? What?
He's...
not dead!
Gecko, Moria and his zombie
army are on the prowl again!
Moria's alive!
On the brawl, they said!
Look, look, it's him!
That's his big, dumb, wonderful face!
I know.
I read the paper.
Then why didn't you tell me? Tell me!
Moria's very important to me!
I don't care. You should!
He's my captain, isn't he?
I thought for sure he died
in Marineford two years ago.
I'm so happy!
If Mori is alive, maybe he
got the gang back together,
and he's already with
Hogback and Absalom too!
Horororo!
I'm going right now!
I can't wait to see him!
Hold on a sec.
I guess I should thank him
for letting me stay here.
Not that I wanted to come
to this kingdom exactly,
Kuma sent me flying here
from thriller. Bark!
After that fight with the Straw Hats,
but I've just been hanging out
for two years, if nothing else.
Moria is persistent
like a horde of zombies;
he employs, say, what
you dare insult Moria?
Ungrateful.
jerk.
I owe him nothing.
Yeah, but you owe me.
Have you forgotten all those
times that I cooked for you?
You cooked, yes, but I cooked more.
Yeah, well, I helped you
with farming stuff, too.
And I gave you
a place to live.
You are the least new thing in the world.
Fine.
I'm leaving.
As you wish.
If you're not mad, I'm not mad.
Take care of yourself.
Don't be nice! Damn it!
I'm trying to storm off here, okay?
Thanks, Fionn.
You did so much for me!
Noisy to the end, huh?
One thing.
Considering the circumstances,
now may be a good time to depart.
The reverie is in session
at Marie Joie, as you know.
They brought up a troubling subject.
Attack!
There is Absalom!
Break him to me now!
I shot them, but they just won't die!
Tell me where Absalom is or else?
I don't know!
You stupid underlings are useless!
Fine, have it your way!
Don't want to deal with me, huh?
Then tell me where to find Teach!
Go to hell!
You aren't listening to me, are you?
Bring me Blackbeard or
you're going to die!
I'm gonna drag you down!
Blackbird!
Awful noisy, Meowth, there.
Pizarro, sir!
It's Gecko Moria!
The former warlord of the sea! Yeah?
Why didn't you let him in?
He broke in, sir!
With his zombie army!
The port is completely destroyed!
Do you know what he's looking for?
Seems he wants to see Commodore teach.
He's looking for his old Gourmet Absalom,
that invisible guy who
was here the other day.
Oh, I see you, chumps,
really aren't working with me, huh?
You think I won't break in there
and wreck you, Maria over here?
I'm so happy you made it.
Absalom, is that really you?
Of course!
In the flesh!
I'm so happy!
I thought you might be
dead! Are you kidding?
I've never felt better!
It's been a while!
I haven't heard a thing about
you since we all split up!
You were making me nervous!
I'm sorry about that, boss, but
this place is a party every day!
I lost track of time having fun.
I forgot to reach out to you
Well, if that's all it is, I'm
just happy to have you back.
Yes, I went a little overboard.
Okay, zombies—that's enough
chaos—go back to the ship I.
ship I
I thought Blackbeard
might have nabbed you.
His crew hunts down people with powers.
That they do.
If someone got your clear clear
fruit, we'd be in big trouble.
Invisibility is a useful power to have.
It can be very deadly in the right hands.
Oh yes, I know that very well.
Very well.
What the hell?
That hurt!
Who caught me?
Where are you?
Come on and fight me!
I trust you know who I am.
Shiryu, isn't it?
You worked at Impel Down,
but joined up with Teach.
Close enough, I suppose.
So, how do you like my new power?
You were invisible, weren't you?
Why do you have Absalom's power?
It can't be.
Ah, but it is, Moria.
My thanks to your old Gourmet.
This will prove quite useful.
Curse you!
If that's not Absalom up
there, who the hell are you?
Maroon!
Devon!
Then tell me, what did you do with him?
Absalom waltzed into our home with a
chip on his shoulder, so we shoved him.
But his body is here, if you want it.
You love a good corpse, right?
How dare you!
I'll make every last one of you pay!
He was my Gourmet!
He was my friend!
You say I love corpses.
You're all gonna be corpses
when I'm done with you!
Oh, if you want to try, be my guest.
We can't have you disturbing
the peace here on Pirate Island.
I recognize that voice.
Go to hell!
In fact, I'll see you there myself!
Yeah, I think I'll pass, thanks.
I'm at my leisure now, you see.
This is a pirate's paradise.
That means it ought to be fun.
You've picked enough fights today.
Ain't that right, guys?
We're here to party!
And if you'd like to party,
you're welcome on my ship!
Well, Moria, you like to parten, right?
You should have more fun.
so did you happen to read the newspaper
today there's never a dull moment lately
on the fourth day of reverie the
captains of the revolutionary army
made their move they risked it all
to take back kuma busting into marie
juan facing off with two navy
admirals rio kugyu and Fujitora must
have been a sight and that's not the
half of it there's also something
going down the land of wano where
the monster kaido lives Straw Hat
and there's been a lot of talk
lately is there along with a whole
slew of hot-blooded punks and hot
on his tail is another emperor
angry as a wet head crazy old big
mom what do you
think will happen next
this is the beginning of
the end you tough guys all
seem to want the throne but
there can only be one king
Oh, my God.
guitar solo
I want to be.
He's as strong as Duke Dog's turn.
He's just as quick and
just as hard-headed, too.
I don't understand, Assure.
You Gar are wasting this power.
Use it to fight to protect the
people of Kuri that Lord Odin loved.
Lord Odin is dead.
Why did you come back after all these
years when the country has gone to hell?
We're here to accomplish
Lord Odin's dream.
A dream that Ugar abandoned.
And now Ugar are selfishly wielding
your sword as your people suffer.
Shut up!
Him!
You speak as if you're so
wise, but you aren't even here!
If there's something you've
got to want to say, say it!
Fuck fire style, fire willow black!
Gentlemen!
That's enough, I think.
Doug Storm!
Ashura!
I thought you were better than this.
I'm disappointed.
You too?
I have watched the land of Wano for the
past two decades since
Lord Odin's sacrifice.
You all show up like no time has passed.
I have no obligation to listen. Now leave!
In fact,
since I'm such a scoundrel, you should be
grateful I don't rob you on your way out.
Have you all forgotten?
This is who we were before
Lord Oden changed that.
Kozuki Oden was a man among men.
One who I would proudly risk
my life for as a samurai.
He is the only one I served.
I do not bow to the Kozuki clan.
I owe this country nothing!
Got that?
Momonosuke.
I was a scoundrel, as you say, myself,
but I have not abandoned my duty.
You will join Ashida.
Of that I will make certain.
You honestly think this country
will welcome the Kozuki clan?
I can't believe your foolish arrogance.
You abandoned our home for 20 years.
You can't compensate for that.
All that we've lost won't return.
Yutia aren't injured, I hope.
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Pardon the interruption.
Yes, Race?
I was able to ascertain
the location of Sir Luffy.
He's confined at the
excavation labor camp in Udon.
As I suspected.
I believe you are the most
suited to deal with this matter.
Say no more!
Otama, please say something.
Hello, Master.
Why am I here?
What happened to me?
It seems you suffered a
vicious attack from Kaido.
Thankfully, these fine doctors found
you and brought you here to safety.
Oh, I see.
Well, thank you all very much.
I am in your debt.
Thankfully, you weren't hurt bad at all.
You'll be better real soon.
Well, that's good to hear.
It sure is.
I, uh, remember I got scared
and passed out right away.
So I don't really know what happened.
Or why someone like Kaido
would attack me like that.
All I can remember is that Horselina
fought super hard to protect me.
All right, Master, let's go!
So you, Karoo, have the power to
turn your enemies into allies?
That must be very handy.
But what happened to Horselina?
And where is Big Bro?
Unfortunately, we didn't
see anyone named Horselina.
And Luffy was...
What?
Big Bro got smashed by Kaido?
And now he's stuck at the camp in Udon.
He needs us!
Hold on, you're still injured.
That doesn't matter.
I'm way more worried about Big
Bro Luffy than some scratches.
He'll be all right.
Our captain always pulls
through, no matter what.
Udang is one of several
regions in the land of Wano.
However,
under the current regime,
most of its inhabitants are criminals,
condemned to the excavation labor camp.
Kaido's lucrative weapons trade is
bolstered by the slave labor in these mines.
It's a dreadful place where the prisoners
are forced to work until they die,
with no hope of escape.
Ha ha ha ha!
No, we don't require geisha.
Do not let anyone approach this room.
Yes, sir.
What a wicked fellow you are!
This is the order sheet for the
next round of armor and weapons,
as wicked as they come, huh!
I suppose, my—that's a lot.
Someone has a war on the horizon, perhaps?
I don't concern myself with
what happens abroad, you know?
That make what they want
and don't ask questions.
My eyes are
too aged—you
must watch them in my stead!
Just stay calm, remain quiet.
Above all else!
Stupid heads
in the way!
the way
Where did they go?
Go up in the attic and get them!
Stop them at any cost!
It's okay!
Just take some deep breaths!
You're not getting away!
You have to stop screaming!
Where'd they go?
Meow?
Meow!
Oh, is it just a cat?
Ah! Uh!
Ah!
Huh?
Huh? Ah! Ahh!
Huh?!
Where did they go?
Why'd you have to freak out like that?
Are you okay?
Oh, Nami.
There's something that
I should have told you.
Find them!
Keep looking around!
Don't let the intruders escape!
The truth is...
I have a fear of sharp objects!
Then how are you a ninja?
Have you forgotten? Hmm?
A mature woman is as
deadly as any weapon.
A fine wind.
Let us catch it.
Ninpo, great kite!
Shinobu, you can fly?
Haven't you found them, you fool?
Did you happen to acquire any intel?
Not really.
Oh, but I saw the
shipment's place and date.
Well done, Onami.
It'll take us straight to a stockpile of
weapons and armor, right for the taking.
Oh my, what's the hustle and bustle
about that's one heck of a line?
Must be a sale seems
like mostly young ladies.
Welcome one, welcome all.
Fresh Sabo coming up.
Okay, next one's ready.
Enjoy, ma 'am.
Wait a sec. Sanji!
It's firm, but tender.
Sweet, savory, and oh-so-juicy.
I'm the third son of five children.
My soba's too delicious.
You won't hate it.
Three, five, two, eight.
And the sum is 18.
And that's today's special.
The noodles are shining!
They really melt in your mouth!
So good!
You're supposed to recruit Samurai!
Thank you, ladies!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
It's a tale of terror!
Castle apparitions are
about spreading a curse!
Don't miss our special
edition covering the
ghost sightings in the northern graveyard!
What's all the hubbub about?
Allow me to go look.
Hitokiri Kamazo
It's him!
His wicked grin is the
last thing you'll ever
see He cuts down any
poor fool in his path.
Who is he, and what does he want?
That one took out my husband!
It's all terrible!
Now, perk up your ears for this one, too!
Have you heard the tale of Ushimitsu Koza?
He appears at the witching
hour to rob from the rich.
But this benevolent bandit shares his
ill-gotten kings with those less fortunate.
Or so they say, at least.
Is he an agent of justice,
or just an agent of chaos?
Who could he be and what's his next target
don't be the last to know
pick up a paper today?
You don't want to miss this
story get it while it's hot
or get left in the dust you
don't have to ask me twice
The reversed crescent moon?
Who gave me this?
Have they truly returned?
The Kozuki clan!
What if it's just those ghosts
that people keep seeing?
We've kept the faith for this long.
Now it's time for action.
I'm gonna do it.
Hmm, it's been too long, I fear.
Ten years ago, I would
have been itching to fight.
Beyond that, where are they
going to get their weapons?
Only samurai can carry a sword.
Citizens are all defenseless.
Even the training halls
have been shut down.
Karate, judo, and every last
weapon has been banned here.
Orochi has eliminated any
chance we'd have to fight back.
I'll beat them with my fists.
I don't care.
I've been waiting so long to do this.
We can't lose.
I'm so ready.
My whole body is shaking.
Sir Luffy.
Raizo.
Keep your voice down.
Is there something wrong?
No friend, it's good.
I bring tidings from the village.
Otama has made a full recovery.
I shall return. Yeah!
Hey Jack, these offerings from
Cootie aren't gonna cut it.
Doflamingo isn't around anymore.
You know who our next business
partner's gonna be, right?
Forgive me, my brothers.
We don't need more dead
weight around here.
We already have Queen.
That's right.
We don't need any more Sexy
when we already have King.
Jack the Stooge, you are on thin ice.
I wouldn't act so tough
if I were you, queen.
You should have those punks
begging for mercy by now.
What's taking so long?
They're gonna be running that prison.
Sorry, I don't accept
criticism from perverts.
What?